Terror on the Prairie is a western, action,
thriller film directed by Michael Polish.
A pioneering family fights back against a gang of vicious outlaws that is
terrorizing them on their newly-built farm on the plains of Montana.
Hattie McAllister, played by Gina Carano.
The Captain, played by Nick Searcy.
Jeb, played by Donald Cerrone.
Gold Tooth, played by Heath Freeman.
The Kid, played by Gabriel-Kane Day-Lewis.
Will, played by Rhys Becker.
Terror on the Prairie is a 2022 American Western film directed
by Michael Polish and written by Josiah Nelson.
It was produced by The Daily Wire and Bonfire Legend, and
distributed by The Daily Wire and Voltage Pictures.
The film follows a family of pioneers as they defend themselves
from a gang of outlaws on the Montana plains.
The film features the cast of Gina Carano as Hattie McAllister, Donald Cerrone as Jeb McAllister, and Nick Searcy starring as The Captain, with Rhys
Jackson Becker, Gabriel-Kane Day Lewis, Tyler Fischer, Heath Freeman, Samaire Armstrong, and Matthias Hues all featured in supporting roles.
Terror on the Prairie was released direct to streaming
on The Daily Wire on June 14, 2022.
Its international theatrical gross was $13,115 from a limited release.
The tone is intense.